<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>docker on No Idiots Allowed Here</title>
    <link>https://chihkaiyu.github.io/tags/docker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in docker on No Idiots Allowed Here</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-TW</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 17:15:55 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://chihkaiyu.github.io/tags/docker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate sameersbn/docker-gitlab to gitlab/gitlab-ce</title>
      <link>https://chihkaiyu.github.io/post/migrate-sameersbn-docker-gitlab-to-gitlab-gitlab-ce/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 17:15:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chihkaiyu.github.io/post/migrate-sameersbn-docker-gitlab-to-gitlab-gitlab-ce/</guid>
      <description>This article records how I migrate GitLab from sameersbn/gitlab to gitlab/gitlab-ce.
Why Why would I bother to migrate it? There are several reasons and here are the most important (for me) ones.
 If you want to enable some functions in GitLab, you would search it from official documents and here comes the pain: you don’t know how to configure it in sameersbn/gitlab. Though the documents of sameersbn/gitlab are quite good, it&amp;rsquo;s sometimes hard to mapping them together sameersbn/gitlab is driven by community and you don’t know when it would give up maintaining it (for the record, sameersbn/docker-gitlab is a excellent project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Ghost with Nginx and MySQL</title>
      <link>https://chihkaiyu.github.io/post/how-to-set-up-ghost-site-with-https/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 23:33:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chihkaiyu.github.io/post/how-to-set-up-ghost-site-with-https/</guid>
      <description>This article will show you how to install and configure Ghost with Nginx and MySQL. In fact, it is that how this blog has been built. This article contains:
 Prerequisite Environment Ghost configuration Nginx configuration MySQL configuration Docker Compose Summary  Prerequisite I use Docker for handling my environment information and I suppose you have the basic knowledge about Docker and Docker Compose. Before you continue, you must ensure both of Docker and Docker Compose have been installed on your machine.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>